A story about first loves and second chances.
Stuck in Love is a drama, comedy, romance film directed by Josh Boone.
An acclaimed writer, his ex-wife, and their teenaged children come to terms with the
complexities of love in all its forms over the course of one tumultuous year.
William Borgens, played by Greg Kinnear.
Erica, played by Jennifer Connelly.
Samantha 'Sam' Borgens, played by Lily Collins.
Rusty Borgens, played by Nat Wolff.
Kate, played by Liana Liberato.
Lou, played by Logan Lerman.
Stuck in Love is a 2012 American romantic comedy-drama film written
and directed by Josh Boone in his directorial debut.
The independent film stars Jennifer Connelly, Greg Kinnear,
Lily Collins, Nat Wolff, and Logan Lerman.
It focuses on the complicated relationships between a successful novelist, played by Kinnear, his
ex-wife (Connelly), their college daughter (Collins), and their teenage son (Wolff).
The film began a limited theatrical release in
the United States on July 5, 2013.
The film explores themes of cheating, parent child
relationship, writing, thanksgiving, north carolina.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.